# SEAN JACKSON

### CONTACT

### **PROFILE**

435-938-1478

I have worked as a freelance composer, manager, and consulted as a private contractor. My goals always include serving others and learning new skills; this has led to me being trusted with responsibility, deadlines, and leadership. Most of all, I love helping others develop and recognize skills in themselves.

refinedgoals
@icloud.com

### SKILLS

Leadership
Team Management
B2B Relationships
Spin Sales Certified
Excel Expert
All major office suites
StaffPad / Studio One

Experience in billing, estimates, mail merge, scheduling, Adobe (Ps, Pr, Ae), VBA, Bash, Macros, Powershell, Netlify, web design, and SEO

### **EDUCATION**

SALT LAKE COM. COLLEGE 2008 - 2013 Maj: Music A.s.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **BUSINESS OWNER**

Scored Films LLC | 2015 - Current

Music composer for film and media. I have done work for Comic-Con, BYUtv, IHC, the SyFy Channel, corporate ads, and other forms of media.

## CONTRACTOR / CONSULTANT

For CleanTelligent and Freelance | Feb 2016 - Current

Report design (in-app and Excel), data entry macros, and UI/UX consulting.

### SUPPORT MANAGER / ENTERPRISE SUPPORT

CleanTelligent | Jun 2013 - Feb 2016

Managed a support department and our largest clients. Traveled and provided video conference trainings to business executives and administrators on implementation of enterprise software, mobile apps, reporting system, and

## FINANCE SSD / VACATION PLANNING COUNSELOR

Marriott Vacations Worldwide | Jul 2005 - Feb 2011

Assisted time-share owners with deed changes, loans, amortization schedules, HOA fees, Marriott Rewards points, and booking reservations.